https://www.communications.cam.ac.uk/campaigns/privacy-notice-our-emails-to-you

How we use your personal information
The University of Cambridge’s Office of External Affairs and Communications uses your personal information to send you emails about news and events in line with your subscription(s). Your name and email address are used with your permission and only to send you information that you have requested. You can withdraw your consent at any time.
We use a third-party provider, Dotdigital EMEA Ltd, to send our emails. We share your name, email address and details of your subscriptions with Dotdigital EMEA Ltd. We gather statistics about email opens and clicks using industry standard technologies (including clear gifs) to help us monitor what content is popular and to improve the content of our emails. For more information, please see Dotdigital’s privacy notice.
Your data is held in the European Economic Area. Where we need to transfer your data outside of the European Economic Area, those transfers are protected either by an 'adequacy decision' by the European Commission (declaring the recipient country as a 'safe' territory for personal data) or by standard contractual clauses adopted by the European Commission (which give obligations for the recipient to safeguard the data).
We are committed to protecting your personal information and being transparent about what information we hold. For further details about how your information is used, how we maintain the security of your information and your rights under data protection law, please read our general data protection statement.
About our websites
Cookies
Privacy policy
© 2020 University of Cambridge
University A-Z
Contact the University
Accessibility
Freedom of information
Spotlight on...
About research at Cambridge
